

CONTACT

Ph: 6369532459

EMAIL:

manojvs0170@gmail.com

ADDRESS

66/70,Main Road, Velampalayam, Kavindapadi,Erode-638455

SKILLS

- Logical Thinking
- Puzzle Solving
- ❖ Team Player
- Good Communication

EXPERTISE

- HTML,CSS & JavaScript
- Tailwind (Basics)
- GitHub
- Aptitude & Soft Skills

MANOJ V.S

One year experienced Aptitude Trainer keen to transition into IT Field (Front End Development / Software Development).
Offers robust logical thinking, problem-solving, and communication skills. Self-trained and Inspired by tech growth, eager to apply my skills and learn in the IT industry.

WORK EXPERIENCE

APTITUDE TRAINER

Sep 2022-Jan 2023 VIT Vellore-SMART Training Resources Pvt Ltd

APTITUDE TRAINER

Jan 2023-June 2023 VIT Vellore-Ethnus Consultancy Services

EDUCATION

Gobi Arts and Science College, Gobichettipalayam

2019-2022

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Percentage-79.94%

Saraswathi Vidhyashram Matric Hr Secondary School, Kavindapadi

2019-HSC - 83% 2017- SSLC - 94%

LANGUAGE

- Tamil
- English

TO CONNECT

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/manoj-v-s-fb17

CssBattle:

https://cssbattle.dev/player/manojvs

GitHub:

https://github.com/manojvs17

PROJECTS

- ✓ E-Commerce Website Created a Website for Table and Chairs Rental Business Using HTML, CSS & JavaScript.
- ✓ Hand Cricket Game Created a
 Interactive game to play with the
 Computer and this game is built with
 Neumorphism theme
- ✓ Eye-catching Designs Created 10+ Colorful designs

ACHIEVEMENTS

- ✓ Ranked within Top 70 among 300k+ global users on CssBattle.dev Replicated 185+ designs in CssBattle.dev, a platform that challenges users to replicate given designs using minimal CSS. Demonstrated advanced CSS proficiency, attention to detail, and ability to optimize code for performance and efficiency.
- ✓ Football-Best Attitude Player Award in KIFA Football Camp(London, UK)
- ✓ Football-University D Zone Winner 2020 & 202